techliance.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy - Techliance LLC | IT Services Company

Your privacy is important to us. Techliance respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web site. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and on every page where personally identifiable information is requested.

### The Information We Collect

The information we receive depends on what you do when you visit our site. Techliance will not collect or retain any information about you personally (that is, your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) unless you choose to provide it to us. On some pages, you can choose to make requests or submit additional information at your discretion. When you visit our site to read or download information, we collect and store only the following: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself only for the purpose described on the page requesting the information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the process or to the extent required by law. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. If you send us e-mail to ask a question we will only use your information to answer your request. Your e-mail address or other contact information will not be provided to any third party without your prior consent. We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site and to share with our business partners. For example, we may tell a partner that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our Web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out a registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured specifically to attract anyone under 13.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

Some online processes allow you to access your personally identifiable information collected online and maintain it by using the account maintenance feature of the specific process. Other online processes collect your information to complete the specific process, without establishing any permanent record. If you are a Techliance Consultant you may contact your Consultant Service Representative to help access and correct your information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to make corrections.

### How to Contact Us

If you have submitted information about yourself through the Techliance Web site or an e-mail message and you would like us to delete that information from our records, please contact us. We will make every effort to delete your personal information from our files.
